My name is Nikita.
Six years ago,
I was taken out of prison...
...and forced by a covert unit
of the government to be an assassin.
Three years ago, I escaped,
and have been hunted ever since.
I was the first recruit to get out.
I'm going to make certain
I'm not the last.
© anoXmous @ http://thepiratebay.sx/user/Zen_Bud
Come on.
Come on, come OH, come on.
Let's go.
- Stay right there.
- Don't move.
She's just a kid.
Taking this one down to solitary.
Watch out. She's a biter.
They're gonna love you down here.
I didn't do it! I didn't do it!
Please. No!
Evening, Alex.
It is Alex, right? Never Alexandra?
Who are you?
Where am I?
Well, you're not in prison anymore.
You're not even in Michigan.
Although we're the only ones
that know that.
Your death was officially ruled a suicide
by the prison coroner on November 1st.
Your ashes are stored right here.
My name's Michael.
I work for the government.
We've decided to give you
a second chance.
Why? Why me?
Because you're a young, attractive,
white female...
...with virtually no personal ties
or a paper trail.
Now, those do exist,
but they're hard to come by.
What really grabbed
our attention, though...
...is how you managed to kill a criminal
we were about to take out.
His name was Kyle, by the way.
He was part of a smuggling ring.
Stand and your wrist breaks.
I didn't kill no one. It was Ronnie.
Your boyfriend's body was found next to
his apartment, dead from an overdose.
No one showed up
to his funeral, either.
Your life is over, Alex.
I'm here to offer you a new one.
But you have to be willing to earn it.
What do I gotta do?
Learn.
How not to sound
like a teen meth whore, for starters.
Learn to stand up straight.
Learn how to walk right.
Learn how to talk right.
Learn how to serve your country
instead of just yourself.
Nikita.
Never seen you before, Nikita.
Who brought you here?
Elena. Yelena?
She said there was a cool party,
so, uh, here I am.
Come, have a drink.
I was kind of hoping to stay dry.
- Why don't we go to the bar?
- As you say, this is a cool party.
If you wanna stay,
you're gonna have to get wet.
That wasn't so bad, was it?
I would have preferred the bar.
It's just that this is gonna make
taking your bodyguard out...
...so much harder.
Target's down. I need extraction
at the servant's entrance.
- Negative. Extraction impossible.
- What?
You always had trouble
listening, didn't you?
Michael, please,
I need to get out of here.
You still don't hear me. I told you.
There is no out.
- Hi, Gary.
- Hi, Gary?
That's a nice touch, honey,
but I ain't buying anything.
All right. Let's try this again.
Hi, Daddy.
Nikita.
Wow. You really let this place go
after Caroline died.
I guess no more foster kids like me
to clean up your crap, either.
You... You broke my frigging wrist. Aah!
Sit up, Gary.
Try to pay attention, okay?
I need to tell you what happened to me
after I ran away.
It starts off like you'd expect
and then it gets a little weird.
- Nikita...
- After I ran away...
...I got with a pretty bad crowd.
I did a lot of drugs.
Anything that made me forget
about you.
Nikita, baby, that was 10 years ago.
It was 11. I'm 27 now.
If you call me "baby" again,
I'll break something else.
They told me I killed a cop.
I don't remember. I've tried to.
I'd just turned 18, so they were able
to charge me with murder one.
I was sentenced to die
by lethal injection.
- No frigging way.
- Trust me.
You'll wanna save your
"no frigging way" for the next part.
My execution was faked by a secret unit
of the government called Division.
They told me they were giving me
a second chance.
They told me
I'd be serving my country.
What they didn't tell me was...
...they were training me
to be an assassin.
They're probably telling some other girl
the same thing right now.
It was a year of training
before my first mission.
Sort of like a military charm school.
Everything to make me
the best killer I could be...
...till I broke one of their rules.
What rule?
I fell in love.
With a civilian. His name was Daniel.
After three months together...
...all I wanted to do was be with him,
live a normal life.
But Division couldn't have that.
So they killed him,
made it look like an accident.
- Why are you telling me all of this?
- You know why, Gary.
They're still after me.
And I know they've been keeping tabs
on you in case I showed up.
It's okay.
I want them to know I'm here.
I want you to tell them everything
I just told you.
I wanna send them a message.
It ends now.
This is surveillance of General
Safwani entering the Wyckland Hotel.
Three bodyguards in his suite,
one in the lobby.
Lobby guard is our weak link.
That's our way in.
We have one shot at this.
If he makes it to the U.N., we fail.
What's the team look like?
It's a four-man op.
One of my recruits, Thorn, is ready for
the field and I was planning on using him.
Percy.
Really?
When?
Look, I'll be right there.
I'm taking you off
Operation Black Arrow...
- ...giving you a new assignment.
- What?
- Nikita.
- Nikita?
She's back on the radar.
Sprung one of our mousetraps.
I want you to hunt her down
and I want you to confirm the kill.
Do you think
you can do that this time?
What do you think?
What?
What are you looking at, bitch?
You're gonna die here, you know that?
What the hell are you doing?
Look, if you don't think
they watch us in here, you're wrong.
Hey, I'd put that down if I were you.
I love it when you hold me like this.
God, chill.
I'm just saying hi to new girl.
This is Jaden. She doesn't think
she's still new here, but she is.
- What's your name?
- What's yours?
This is Thorn. He's a pro because
he's about to go on his first mission.
Shut up.
Look, we're recruits, just like you.
I've been in almost a year.
They brought Jaden in
about two months ago.
None of us are volunteers.
Meaning, whatever they got on you...
...whatever your big bad past is,
it's nothing we haven't heard before.
Meaning, we need to stick together
if we're gonna make it through training.
Trust me.
Now, you can start
by telling us your name.
Alex.
Amanda is ready to see you.
Yeah, well, understand this,
FBI's paying for all this damage...
...because this is going a bit beyond
the call of duty.
Hey.
She didn't go into the bathroom.
Did she say anything else?
We've been over this
50 frigging times.
What do you think she meant by
"it ends now"?
I don't know. Ha.
Because I kind of lost focus when she
went into the whole James Bond thing.
I'm talking about her tone.
Was she tired? Did she wanna surrender?
Did she wanna give up?
Man, I wasn't concentrating on her tone
because my wrist...
I'm all set.
Don't worry, I'll clean him.
Roan, I was talking to him.
Nikita knew
what we would have to do.
I don't think she liked this guy.
If the job's too stressful, let it go.
You know I can't, Daniel.
The airline will find another consultant.
Too much would have to change.
How much?
About this much?
Now, don't get too excited.
It's just the box.
Daniel.
It's beautiful.
- I think you broke a rib.
- I did?
- Which one?
- Well...
This one?
Keep going. I'm not sure.
- Oh. Hey.
- Ha, ha.
Promise me something.
Right now, anything.
Promise me it's not a dream
that I'm gonna wake up from tomorrow.
It's Nikita. It's definitely her.
I got a hit on the pressure sensor
at Greenlawn, pulled up AthenaSat. Boom.
Took her three years
but she's finally paying her respects.
Well, she's finally snapped.
Look, go ahead and assemble a team.
We're in closer proximity to her
than Michael is.
She had a good run.
Won't be another one like her.
Don't be so sure.
Hello?
Well, don't just stand there, Alex.
Try it on.
- You'll find it fits perfectly.
- I don't wear stuff like this.
As a style choice,
or because you're not used to it?
Because it's ugly.
And you're beautiful.
Michael was right about that much.
So what?
You're supposed to teach me
how to walk and talk?
- Chew with my mouth closed?
- My name is Amanda.
And I'm the one who's going to show you
how to embrace your beauty.
And use it to your advantage.
Your journey begins right here,
in this chair.
I'm not smearing that crap
on my face.
It's not like this will be the first time
you've reinvented yourself, Alex.
We're all very impressed with your accent,
or lack thereof.
How?
Well, based on your age now...
...and the five years or so you'd have
to work to lose your accent...
...it wasn't hard
to answer the question...
...what kind of 14-year-old Ukrainian girl
purchases a forged identity?
Someone who was brought here
against her will, on a boat...
...with many other girls just like her?
Not like me. I escaped.
Your captors, yes,
but not the junk they hooked you on.
You're a survivor, Alex.
You made it through hell,
you'll make it through this.
All I'm here to show you is
you don't have to be hard to survive.
Sometimes vulnerability can be
our greatest weapon.
Position is unchanged.
Use caution, she will be armed.
Bye, Nikki.
Execute.
Target on the move.
North gate. North gate.
Radio back when you have visual.
Good boy, Birkhoff.
What are you gonna do?
You'll see.
Congratulations, Birkhoff.
You found me.
What is that, truth serum?
It's pain desensitizer.
I don't want you passing out on me.
So, what, you gonna torture me?
Is that it?
Not if you tell me
what I need to know.
I always told you you were hot,
you know that.
I want access to Division's network.
Logins, passwords.
Bitch, just skip to the part
where you kill me.
No.
Seriously, do it.
If I give you those codes,
Percy will kill me.
Shut up.
What do you want
with the network, anyway?
It's not like it was any help to us
finding where you've been hiding out.
- I'm not hiding anymore.
- Then what are you doing?
You're not trying to come at us,
are you?
Oh, man.
Nikki...
Nikki, you're insane.
Don't call me Nikki.
Then don't call me "nerd."
Remember you used to call me that?
"Patch me through to Michael, nerd."
"This computer's busted.
Fix it, nerd."
Place ain't the same without you, babe.
Then let's burn it down.
You seriously think you can burn down
Division all on your own?
Who says I'm on my own?
So you're playing
for the other side now?
Well, if you've got such big guns
on your side backing you up...
...what do you need me for?
Well, because they may be able
to get me the intel I need...
...but I know you can get it.
Well, then,
we're right back where we started.
Just understand...
...if you do this...
...you're gonna have to kill your way
through a whole lot of people you know.
Starting with me, Nikki.
We've got Birkhoff.
The signal interference is gone.
His tracking implant's back online.
Well, let's hope it's still inside him.
She's long gone, guys.
Good hustle, though. Very nice.
Someone wanna get me off this?
Michael, little help here?
Oh, look, all cleaned up.
You know they say
Amanda can pretty up a pig.
Then you should go see her sometime.
He's intense.
He's about to go on his first op.
He's just stressed.
Even though he won't admit it.
Are you guys...?
- Division doesn't allow relationships.
- Who said anything about a relationship?
New girl's a spitfire, Thorn.
Maybe you can get him to give it up.
We wanna know
about Operation Black Arrow.
- Look, I told you, that's...
- That's classified?
God, you sound like one of them now.
Come on, I know it's going down
at the Wyckland Hotel.
Who told you that?
This is spy school, Thorn.
I spied on you Googling stuff
in the computer lab.
The Wyckland Hotel,
some West African VIP...
...General Sawani or Saweenie
or something.
- You could get in trouble for that.
- Please, who am I gonna tell?
I'm just jealous
you get to smoke someone.
I mean, what are we here for, right?
What, you disagree?
What are we here for, really?
Oh, man. Is she playing with me?
At least half of our missions
are counterintel.
Deep cover infiltration,
stealing secrets...
- And the other half?
- You're here to kill for the Man, honey.
They're gonna teach you to kill with
a gun, teach you to kill with your nails.
They're gonna tell you who to kill
and when to kill them.
And if you don't deliver,
they're gonna kill you.
Jaden, you're up.
She's running out of options.
Ah. I mean, if she can't crack me, there's
no way she's gonna crack this place.
- She say who she was working for?
- No.
Honestly, I think it's a bluff.
I think she's on her own.
I mean, she was a wreck.
I was able to turn the tables
on her easy.
Yeah. Was that before or after
she duct-taped you...
...to that springy rocking horse?
You're alive
because she wanted you that way.
We need to suspend all operations
until we can contain this.
As long as she's out there,
she's a threat.
Threats are what we put down
using our resources.
- Nikita is a complication.
- If you believe Birkhoff.
I'm telling the truth, Michael.
And she didn't kill me
because she likes me.
I think you're just jealous
she didn't ask about you.
- Where are you going?
- Joint-intelligence fundraiser.
Gotta put in an appearance.
For the record?
I'm not gonna let a piece of street trash
slow this operation. Not for one minute.
All operations are go,
including Black Arrow.
Tomorrow's
peace summit at the United Nations...
...aims to end civil war
in a region plagued by warring factions.
He's going to eat. One hour.
Get the car ready.
The car is ready. Lobby's clear.
Take your time.
Hey. This is my water.
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought this was left here
by another guest.
- Would you like a new one?
- No.
Towel, sir?
Four is down.
Gardiah. Gardiah, what's wrong?
Gardiah, what's wrong?
Go check it out.
That should do it.
I hope so.
That could have gone better.
Gardiah down.
Gardiah down. Gardiah down.
You, show your hands.
I'll kill you.
General, wake up.
You're at the United Nations.
What are you doing?
You can't do this to me.
Do what, save your life?
I hope you noticed.
A kill squad tried to take you out before
you could make it to your peace summit.
You're American.
I'm an ally of the United States.
The United States didn't attack you.
One of their weapons did.
A weapon they've lost control of,
a unit called Division.
I don't understand.
It's simple. Your country's rich with oil
but you don't own any of it.
The companies that drill it do. They know
the minute you stabilize your country...
...the second you end civil war,
you'll kick them out.
Those companies contracted Division
to kill you.
How do you know this? Who are you?
I'm someone who wants to see
Division fail.
Peace.
Hey.
Well, hello, Alex.
It's good to see you again.
I was, um...
I was wondering if you could help me.
Of course. It's what I'm here for.
Tell me how I can help.
- You can help me get out of here.
- Alex...
Shut up.
We're gonna walk to the elevator,
you're gonna open it, I'm gonna get in it.
And go where?
I didn't kill anyone.
I don't wanna kill anyone.
But I swear to God, if you don't get up
right now, I will kill you.
The elevator doesn't lead to freedom.
- Just another room.
- What?
The more you try to get out...
...the more you realize
there will always be another room.
I don't know
who told you these things, Alex.
We're not murderers, we're protectors.
We protect our home.
What home?
Home is wherever you stop running.
You haven't been home for so long...
...you probably forget
what it even feels like or how it begins.
It begins with a promise.
You promise to put down the shears,
I promise to forget this ever happened.
And we begin again.
Welcome home.
- Glad you're able to be here, Percy.
- That makes one of us.
John, what did you wanna tell me
that I couldn't hear on the phone?
The, uh, CIA has made my committee
aware of some very high-level
espionage activities.
Kidnappings, assassinations.
It's the work
of a skilled intelligence network...
...but we can't attribute it
to any of our enemies, or allies.
You come across anything like that?
Not that I'm aware of.
Hey, hey, you work for us.
Remember that.
I work for whoever happens to be sitting
in your chair.
That person tends to come and go.
Black Arrow was blown.
Nikita sabotaged the op.
Then what are you doing here?
Find her.
I need to pull in assets.
We trained Nikita to be a ghost.
Finding her when she doesn't want
to be found is next to impossible.
Hey, guys.
- Thought I heard my name.
- How did you get in here?
Front door, like you.
- Who are you bothering now?
- Ha, ha.
What, I can't mingle?
Well, she's been behaving herself,
senator.
- I'm sorry, I didn't get your name.
- Oh, Nikita.
Beautiful.
- Your daughter?
- Family friend.
- Yes. Shall...?
- Damn.
- I'm sorry.
- You better get some seltzer on that.
- That's right, that's right. This way, sir.
- I'll wait for you.
If you think Senator Markus
is gonna be leverage, he's not.
He's just my ticket tonight.
Found out what escort service he used
and I worked it so I was his date.
Well, you've been planning this
for a while, huh?
I want you to know I can get to you
and hit you where it hurts the most.
- My feelings?
- Your funding.
Tonight was just a taste.
I'm gonna take you apart,
piece by piece, mission by mission.
Didn't you accompany me
to one of these once?
Yes. Five years ago.
You needed some arm candy
to distract some VIP.
- I'm surprised you remember that.
- I remember everything.
Oh.
Which is why I decided to bring along
a little backup tonight.
And why I'm afraid
I'm gonna have to decline your offer.
You know, this doesn't
have to be awkward.
Why don't you just take my arm
and we'll go right out that door?
You can go quiet or the other way.
- Your choice.
- No, Percy, it's yours.
And you just made it.
All right, stay here.
Nikita.
Safety on, toss it behind you.
Don't turn around.
Get down on the ground, slowly.
Spread your arms and your legs.
Just like old times, huh?
Shut up.
You were free. You had gotten out.
You were gone.
What the hell are you doing here?
Someone has to stop Percy.
If Percy goes down, he has no problem
taking everybody down with him.
This country will not recover.
- Do you want that?
- What are you talking about?
I'm talking about evidence
of every job Division has had...
...locked away in encrypted files,
hidden all over the world.
So he gets a free pass
to keep training slaves to kill for him?
Spare me, Nikita.
I know you're in this for revenge.
Can you blame me?
You know firsthand what it feels like.
Have the thing you love most in life
taken away from you.
It wasn't your life. It was your cover.
I warned you not to get
emotionally attached.
You mean the way you did? With me?
Don't. Don't.
Michael, I know why
you're staying there.
You wanna protect the other recruits
the way you protected me.
I can't protect you anymore.
Then let me go. Or stop me now.
I'll give you a head start.
If we meet again,
I can't promise what will happen.
I can.
It's a good wound.
They'll think you tried to stop me.
I'm just trying to protect you.
Nikita is our new priority target.
Threat level six.
Every operative engaged at that level
or lower will be working on this full-time.
Michael will be heading the detail.
Amanda will be directing
our overseas assets.
There's a handful of organizations
who could intercept our intelligence.
Someone is running her
and I want to know who.
Bring me her head
and bring me all of theirs.
This is war.
Now get to work.
Never gonna get this.
Yeah, someone else told me that once.
She was wrong too.
Remember, you're just getting started.
Damn right.
Here we go.
© anoXmous @ http://thepiratebay.sx/user/Zen_Bud