My name is Nikita.
6 years ago I was taken out of prison
and forced by a covert unit
of the government to be an assassin.
3 years ago, I escaped,
and have been hunted
ever since.
I was the first recruit
to get out.
I'm going to make certain
I'm not the last.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Come on!
Come on, come on, come on.
Aahh!
Stay right there!
Don't move!
She's just a kid.
Taking this one
down to solitary.
Watch out... She's a biter.
They're going to love you here.
I didn't do it!
Evening, Alex.
It is Alex, right?
Never Alexandra.
Who are you?
Where am I?
Well, you're not
in prison anymore.
You're not even in Michigan,
although we're the only
ones that know that.
Your death was officially
ruled a suicide
by the prison coroner
on November first.
Your ashes are stored
right here.
My name's Michael.
I work for the government.
We've decided to give
you a second chance.
Why?
Why me?
Because you're a young
attractive white female
with virtually no personal
ties or paper trail.
Now, those do exist,
but they're hard to come by.
What really grabbed
our attention, though,
how you managed to kill a criminal
we were about to take out.
Aah! Ow!
His name was Kyle, by the way.
He was part of a smuggling ring.
Stand and your wrist breaks.
I didn't kill no one!
It was Ronnie!
Your boyfriend's body was
found next to his apartment,
dead from an overdose.
No one showed up
to his funeral, either.
Your life is over, Alex.
I'm here to offer you
a new one.
But you have to be
willing to earn it.
What do I gotta do?
Learn.
How not to sound like a teen
meth whore, for starters.
Learn to stand up straight.
Learn how to walk right.
Learn how to talk right.
Learn how to serve
your country...
Instead of just yourself.
Chica.
You.
Como te llamas?
Nikita.
Never seen you before, Nikita.
Who brought you here?
Elena. Yelena?
She said there was
a cool party,
so, uh, here I am.
Venga.
Come.
Have a drink.
I was kinda hoping to stay dry.
Why don't we go to the bar?
As you say,
this is a cool party.
If you want to stay, you're
going to have to get...wet.
That wasn't so bad, was it?
I would have preferred the bar.
It's just that
this is going to make
taking your bodyguard out
so much harder.
Como?
Target is down! I need extraction
at the service entrance.
Negative.
Extraction impossible.
What?
You always had trouble
listening, didn't you?
Michael! Please,
I need to get out of here.
Still don't hear me.
I told you.
There is no out.
Hi, Gary.
"Hi, Gary"?
That's a nice touch, honey,
but I ain't buying anything.
Ah, all right.
Let's try this again.
Hi, daddy.
Nikita...
Wow.
You really let this place
go after Caroline died.
I guess no more
foster kids like me
to clean up your crap, either.
You... you broke
my friggin' wrist! Ah!
Sit up, Gary.
Try to pay attention, ok?
I need to tell you what happened
to me after I ran away.
It starts off
like you'd expect,
and then it gets
a little weird.
Nikita...
After I ran away,
I got with a pretty bad crowd.
Did a lot of drugs.
Anything that made me
forget about you.
Nikita, baby,
that was 10 years ago.
It was 11. I'm 27 now.
If you call me baby again,
I'll break something else.
They told me I killed a cop.
I don't remember.
I've tried to.
I'd just turned 18,
so they were able to
charge me with murder one.
I was sentenced to die
by lethal injection.
No friggin' way.
Trust me.
You'll want to save your "no
friggin' way" for the next part,
where my execution
was faked by a secret unit
of the government
called "Division".
They told me they were
giving me a second chance.
They told me I'd be
serving my country.
What they didn't tell me
was they were training me
to be an assassin.
They're probably telling some other
girl the same thing right now.
It was a year of training
before my first mission, sort of
like a military charm school.
Everything to make me
the best killer I could be...
till I broke
one of their rules.
What rule?
I fell in love.
With a civilian.
His name was Daniel.
After 3 months together,
all I wanted to do
was be with him.
Live a normal life
but Division
couldn't have that,
so they killed him and made
it look like an accident.
Why are you telling me
all of this?
You know why, Gary.
They're still after me.
And I know they've been
keeping tabs on you
in case I showed up.
It's ok.
I want them to know I'm here.
I want you to tell them
everything I just told you.
I want to send them a message.
It ends now.
This is surveillance
of general Safwani
entering the Wyckland hotel.
3 bodyguards in his suite,
one advance guard in the lobby.
Lobby guard is our weak link.
That's our way in.
We have one shot at this.
If he makes it to
the U.N., we fail.
What's the team look like?
It's a 4-man op.
One of my recruits, Thom,
is ready for the field.
And I was planning on using...
Percy.
Really?
When?
No, I'll be right there.
I'm taking you off
operation black arrow.
Giving you a new assignment.
What?
Nikita? Nikita.
She's back on the radar.
Sprung one of our mouse traps.
I want you to hunt her down,
and I want you
to confirm the kill.
Do you think you can
do that this time?
What do you think?
What?
What are you looking at, bitch?
You're going to die here,
you know that?
What the hell are you doing?!
If you don't think they watch
us in here, you're wrong!
Hey.
I'd put that down
if I were you.
I love it when
you hold me like this.
God. Chill.
Just saying hi to the new girl.
This is Jaden.
She doesn't think
she's still new
here, but she is.
What's your name?
What's yours?
This is Thom.
He's a pro,
'cause he's about to go
on his first mission.
Shut up.
Look, we're recruits,
just like you.
I've been in almost a year,
they brought Jaden in
about 2 months ago.
None of us are volunteers.
Meaning, whatever they're got on you,
whatever your big bad past is,
it's nothing we haven't
heard before.
Meaning we need
to stick together
if we're going to make
it through training.
Trust me.
Now, you can start
by telling us your name.
Alex.
Amanda's ready to see you.
Yeah, well understand this...
FBI is paying
for all this damage,
'cause this is going
a bit beyond
the call of duty.
Hey!
She didn't go
into the bathroom!
Did she say anything else?
Man, we've been over this
50 freakin' times already.
What do you think she meant
by "it ends now"?
I don't know.
'Cause I kinda lost focus
once she went into the
whole James Bond thing.
I'm talking about her tone.
Was she tired?
Did she want to surrender?
Did she want to give up?
Man, I wasn't concentrating
on her tone,
'cause my wrist...
I'm all set.
Don't worry, I'll clean it.
Roan.
I was talking to him.
Nikita knew what
we would have to do.
I don't think
she liked this guy.
Your job's too stressful.
Let it go.
You know I can't, Daniel.
The airline will find
another consultant.
Too much would have to change.
How much?
♪ Trying to talk
my way out of this ♪
Like this much?
Don't get too excited,
it's just the box.
Daniel!
It's beautiful!
I think you broke a rib.
I did?
Which one?
This one? Well...
Keep going, I'm not sure.
Oh! Hey!
Promise me something.
Right now, anything.
Promise me it's not a dream...
I'm going to wake up from
tomorrow. Right now, anything.
Shh, shh, shh.
It's Nikita.
It's definitely her. I got a hit on the
pressure senser, pulled up athenasat, boom.
Took her 3 years, but she's
finally paying her respects.
That, or she's finally snapped.
Go ahead and assemble a team.
We're in closer proximity
to her here than Michael is.
She had a good run.
Won't be another one like her.
Don't be so sure.
Hello?
Well, don't just stand
there, Alex, try it on.
You'll find it fits perfectly.
I don't wear stuff like this.
As a style choice, or because
you're not used to it?
Because it's ugly.
And you're beautiful.
Michael was right
about that much.
So what?
You're the one that's
supposed to teach me
how to walk and talk,
chew with my mouth closed?
My name is Amanda,
and I'm the one who's
going to show you
how to embrace your beauty
and use it to your advantage.
Your journey begins right
here in this chair.
I'm not smearing that crap
on my face.
It's not like this
will be the first time
you've reinvented
yourself, Alex.
I'm very impressed wit your
accent, or lack thereof.
How?
Well, based on your age now,
and taking into account
the 5 years or so
you'd have to work
to lose your accent.
It wasn't hard to
answer the question
what kind of 14 year
old Ukrainian girl
purchases a forged identity?
Someone who was brought here
against her will, on a boat,
with many and the girls just like her.
Not like me.
I escaped.
Your captors, yes, but not
the junk they hooked you on.
You're a survivor, Alex.
You made it through hell,
you'll make it through this.
All I'm here to show you is you
don't have to be hard to survive.
Sometimes vulnerability
can be our greatest weapon.
Position is unchanged.
Use caution. She will be armed.
Bye, Niki.
Execute.
Target on the move!
Target on the move.
North gate, north gate!
Radio back when
you have visual.
Good boy, Birkhoff.
What are you gonna do?
You'll see.
Ahh.
Congratulations, Birkhoff.
You found me.
What is that?
Truth serum?
It's pain desensitizer.
I don't want you
passing out on me.
So, what, you gonna torture me?
Is that it?
Not if you tell me
what I need to know.
Well, I always told you
you were hot.
You know that.
I want access
to Division's network.
Log-ins, passwords.
Bitch, just skip to the part
where you kill me.
No.
Seriously, do it!
Because if I give you
those codes,
Percy will kill me.
Shut up!
What do you want with the network?
Finding where it was
you've been hiding out.
I'm not hiding anymore.
Then what are you doing?
You're not trying
to come at us, are you?
Man. Niki...
Niki, you're insane.
Don't call me Niki.
Then don't call me nerd.
Remember you used
to call me that?
"Patch me through
to Michael, nerd.
This computer's busted,
fix it, nerd."
Place ain't the same
without you, babe.
Then let's burn it down.
You seriously think you can burn
down Division all on your own?
Who says I'm on my own?
So you playing
for the other side now?
Well, if you got such big guns
on your side backing you up,
what do you need me for?
Well, because they may be able
to get me the intel I need.
But I know you can get it.
Well, then we're right back
where we started.
Just understand,
if you do this,
you're going to have
to kill your way through
a whole lot of people you know.
Starting with me.
Niki.
We've got Birkhoff.
The signal interference
is gone.
His tracking implant's
back online.
Let's hope it's still
inside him.
She's long gone, guys.
Good hustle, though.
Very nice.
Someone want
to get me off this?
Michael, a little help here?
Ah, look.
All cleaned up.
You know, they say Amanda
can pretty up a pig.
You should go see her sometime.
He's intense.
He's about to go on
his first op.
He's just stressed.
Heh. Even though
he won't admit it.
You guys...
Division doesn't allow
relationships.
Who said anything
about a relationship?
New girl's a spitfire, Thom.
Maybe you can get him
to give it up.
We want to know about
operation Black Arrow.
Look, I told you, that's...
That's classified? God.
You sound like one of them now.
Come on. I know it's going
down at the Wyckland hotel.
Who told you that?
This is a spy school, Thom.
I spied on you googling
stuff at the computer lab.
The Wyckland hotel,
some west African V.I.P.
General Sawani or
Sa-weenie or something.
You can get in trouble for that.
Please.
Who am I going to tell?
I'm just jealous
you get to smoke someone.
I mean, what are we
here for, right? What?
You disagree?
What are we here for?
Really?
Ah, man.
Is she playing with me?
At least half of our
missions are counter intel.
Deep cover infiltrations...
and the other half?
You're here to kill
for the man, honey.
They're going to teach you
to kill with a gun.
They're going to teach you to kill
with your nails,
they're going to tell you
who to kill
and when to kill them.
And if you don't deliver,
they're going to kill you.
Jaden, you're up.
She's running out of options.
Ah. I mean,
if she can't crack me,
there's no way she's going
to crack this place.
She say who was working for?
No.
Honestly, I think it's a bluff.
I think she's on her own.
I mean, you should have
seen her, she was a wreck.
I was able to turn
the tables on her easy.
Yeah, was that before or after
she duct-taped you to that
springy rocking horse?
The only reason
why you're alive
is because she wanted you that way.
We need to suspend
all operations
until we can contain this.
As long as she's out
there, she's a threat.
Threats are what we put down
using our resources.
Nikita is a complication.
If you believe Birkhoff.
I'm telling the truth, Michael.
And she didn't kill me
because she likes me.
Think you're just jealous
she didn't ask about you.
Where are you going?
Joint intelligence
fundraiser tonight.
I've gotta put in
an appearance.
For the record,
I'm not going to let a piece
of street trash
slow down this operation.
Not for one minute.
All operations are go,
including Black Arrow.
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ ooh ♪
♪ how, how did I do this?♪
♪ me, I put the wall
around my heart ♪
♪ why didn't I notice ♪
♪ such a cold detachment
from the start? ♪
♪ without joy, joy,
joy in the rain ♪
♪ I could feel
forever the same ♪
♪ ooh ♪
The united
nations aims to end civil war
in a region plagued
by warring factions.
He's going to eat.
One hour.
Get the car ready.
The car is ready.
Lobby's clear.
Take your time.
Hey!
This is my water.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought this was left here
by another guest.
Would you like a new one?
No.
Towel, sir?
Four is down.
Gardiah.
Gardiah, what's wrong?
Go check it out.
That should do it.
Phew.
I hope so.
That could have gone better.
Gardiah is out.
Gardiah's out, Gardiah's out.
No, show your...
General,
wake up. You're at
the united nations.
What are you doing?
You can't do this to me.
Do what, save your life?
I hope you noticed.
The kill squad
just tried to take you out
before you could make it to
your peace summit tomorrow.
You're an American.
I'm an ally of
the United States.
The United States
didn't attack you.
One of their weapons did;
A weapon they've
lost control of.
A unit called Division.
I don't understand.
It's simple.
Your country's rich with oil
but you don't own any of it.
The companies that drill it do.
They know they minute that
you stabilize your country,
the second you end civil war,
you'll kick 'em out.
Those companies contracted
Division to kill you.
How do you know this?
Who are you?
I'm someone who wants
to see Division fail.
Peace.
Well, hello, Alex.
It's good to see you again.
I was, um...
I was wondering
if you could help me.
Well, of course.
It's what I'm here for.
Tell me how I can help.
You can help me get out of here.
Alex... Shut up!
We're going to walk
to the elevator,
you're going to open it,
and I'm going to get in it.
And go where?
I didn't kill anyone.
But I swear to God,
if you don't get up right now,
I will kill you.
The elevator doesn't
lead to freedom.
Just another room.
What?
The more you try to get out,
the more you realize
there will always be
another room.
I don't know who told
you these things, Alex.
We're not murderers.
We're protectors.
We protect our home.
What home?
Home is wherever
you stop running.
You haven't been
home for so long,
you probably forget what
it even feels like.
Well, it begins...
It begins with a pro.
You promise
to put down the shears.
I promise to forget
this ever happened,
and we begin again.
Welcome home.
Glad you're able to be
here tonight, Percy.
Makes one of us.
John, what did you want
to tell me
that I couldn't hear
on the phone?
The CIA has made
my committee aware
of some very high level
espionage activities.
Kidnappings, assassinations.
It's clearly the work of a
skilled intelligence network.
But we can't attribute it
to any one of our enemies.
Or allies.
You come across
anything like that?
Not that I'm aware of.
Hey, you work for us,
remember that.
I work for whoever happens
to be sitting in your chair.
That person tends
to come and go.
Black Arrow was blown.
Nikita sabotaged the op.
Then what the hell are
you doing here find her!
We need to pull in
assets from the field.
We trained Nikita
to be a ghost.
Finding her when she
doesn't want to be found
is next to impossible.
Hey, guys.
I thought I heard my name.
How did you get in here?
Front door.
Like you.
Who are you bothering now?
What, I can't mingle?
She's been behaving
herself, senator.
I'm sorry, I didn't
get your name.
Oh. Nikita.
Beautiful.
Your daughter?
Family friend.
Yes. Shall...
I'm sorry.
We better get some
seltzer on that.
That's right, that's right.
This way, senator.
If you think senator Marcus
is going to be leverage,
he's not.
He was just my ticket tonight.
I found out what
escort service he used
and I worked it
so I was his date.
Well, you've been planning
this for a while, huh?
I want you to know
I can get to you,
and hit you where
it hurts the most.
My feelings?
Your funding.
Tonight was just a taste.
I'm going to take you apart,
piece by piece,
mission by mission.
Didn't you accompany me
to one of these once?
Yes.
5 years ago.
You needed some arm candy
to distract some v.I.P.
I'm surprised
you remember that.
I remember everything.
Ah.
Which is why I decided to bring
along a little back-up tonight.
And I'm afraid I'm going to
have to decline your offer.
You know this doesn't
have to be awkward.
Just take my arm and we'll
go right out that door.
We can do it quiet,
or the other way.
Your choice.
No, Percy, it's yours.
And you just made it.
Ah, stay here.
Nikita!
Safety on.
Toss it behind you,
don't turn around.
Get down on the ground.
Slowly.
Spread your arms and your legs.
Just like old times, huh?
Shut up.
You were free.
You had gotten out,
you were gone.
What the hell
are you doing back here?
Someone has to stop Percy.
If Percy goes down,
he has no problem
taking everybody down with him.
This country will not recover.
Do you want that?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about evidence
of every job Division has had,
locked away in encrypted files,
hidden all over the world.
So he gets a free pass?
Keep training slaves
to kill for him?
Spare me, Nikita.
I know you're in this
for revenge.
You blame me?
You know firsthand
what it feels like.
Have the thing you love most
in life taken away from you.
It wasn't your life.
It was your cover.
I warned you not to get
emotionally attached.
You mean the way you did...
With me?
Don't. Don't.
Michael, I know why
you're staying there.
You want to protect
the other recruits
the way you protected me.
I can't protect you anymore.
Then let me go.
Or stop me now.
I'll give you a head start.
If we meet again I can't
promise what will happen.
I can.
It's a good wound.
They'll think you tried to stop me.
Just trying to protect you.
Nikita is our new
priority target.
Threat level 6.
Every operative engaged
at that level or lower
will be working on this
full time.
Mike will be heading
the detail.
Amanda will be directing
our overseas assets.
There's really only
a handful of organizations
who could intercept
our intelligence.
Someone is running her,
and I want to know who.
Bring me her head
and bring me all of theirs.
This is war!
Now get to work.
I'm never gonna get this.
Yeah, someone else
told me that once.
She was wrong, too.
Remember, you're just
getting started.
Damn right.
Here we go.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com